{
  "uniqueId": "english definitions 16",
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "STRICT",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "a ladle that has a cup with a long handle  ",
      "answer": "dipper"
    },
    {
      "question": "the doctrine that reality consists of two basic opposing elements, often taken to be mind and matter (or mind and body), or good and evil  ",
      "answer": "dualism"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose job is to dye cloth  ",
      "answer": "dyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "an alphabetical list of technical terms in some specialized field of knowledge",
      "answer": "glossary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the thin serous membrane around the lungs and inner walls of the chest  ",
      "answer": "pleura"
    },
    {
      "question": "leafless East Indian vine",
      "answer": "soma"
    },
    {
      "question": "not affiliated in a trade union",
      "answer": "unorganized"
    },
    {
      "question": "uncertain of all claims to knowledge  ",
      "answer": "agnostic"
    },
    {
      "question": "oily poisonous liquid amine obtained from nitrobenzene and used to make dyes and plastics and medicines  ",
      "answer": "aniline"
    },
    {
      "question": "as if struck dumb with astonishment and surprise",
      "answer": "dumbfounded"
    },
    {
      "question": "a craftsman skilled in operating machine tools  ",
      "answer": "machinist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short musket of wide bore with a flared muzzle  ",
      "answer": "blunderbuss"
    },
    {
      "question": "the invention of a scheme or story to suit some purpose",
      "answer": "concoction"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a giddy light-headed manner",
      "answer": "dizzily"
    },
    {
      "question": "add details to  ",
      "answer": "embroider"
    },
    {
      "question": "not holy because unconsecrated or impure or defiled  ",
      "answer": "profane"
    },
    {
      "question": "the central area in a building",
      "answer": "atrium"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or resembling gladiators or their combat",
      "answer": "gladiatorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "the blocking of one sensation resulting from the presence of another sensation",
      "answer": "masking"
    },
    {
      "question": "a significant event in your life (or in a project)  ",
      "answer": "milestone"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an abundant manner",
      "answer": "abundantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "(bread and pastries) cooked by dry heat (as in an oven)",
      "answer": "baked"
    },
    {
      "question": "cry softly, as of pigeons  ",
      "answer": "coo"
    },
    {
      "question": "force into some kind of situation, condition, or course of action",
      "answer": "embroil"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of a group of hard crystalline minerals that consist of aluminum silicates of potassium or sodium or calcium or barium  ",
      "answer": "feldspar"
    },
    {
      "question": "be suspended over or hang over",
      "answer": "overhang"
    },
    {
      "question": "device that reflects radiation  ",
      "answer": "reflector"
    },
    {
      "question": "Asian pepper plant whose dried leaves are chewed with betel nut (seed of the betel palm) by southeast Asians  ",
      "answer": "betel"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or having or characterized by hue  ",
      "answer": "chromatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "strip the skin off  ",
      "answer": "flay"
    },
    {
      "question": "an executioner who beheads the condemned person  ",
      "answer": "headsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the vast grassy plains of northern Argentina  ",
      "answer": "pampas"
    },
    {
      "question": "drop sharply",
      "answer": "plummet"
    },
    {
      "question": "so undesirable as to be incapable of arousing envy",
      "answer": "unenviable"
    },
    {
      "question": "durable goods for home or office use  ",
      "answer": "appliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clay-like mineral",
      "answer": "bauxite"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various ornamental climbing plants of the genus Clematis usually having showy flowers  ",
      "answer": "clematis"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing by example  ",
      "answer": "exemplification"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occurrence of a water flow resulting from sudden rain or melting snow  ",
      "answer": "freshet"
    },
    {
      "question": "without consideration",
      "answer": "inconsiderately"
    },
    {
      "question": "hung or decorated with tapestry  ",
      "answer": "tapestried"
    },
    {
      "question": "wavelike motion",
      "answer": "undulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "not gained by merit or labor or service",
      "answer": "unearned"
    },
    {
      "question": "an agricultural laborer in Arab countries  ",
      "answer": "fellah"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of or tending to change in form or quality or nature",
      "answer": "mutable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a raging and rapidly spreading conflagration  ",
      "answer": "wildfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "the fleshy part of the human body that you sit on",
      "answer": "buttocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or marked by communism",
      "answer": "communist"
    },
    {
      "question": "vary in order to spread risk or to expand",
      "answer": "diversify"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who has entered a religious order but has not taken final vows  ",
      "answer": "novitiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "wash off soap or remaining dirt  ",
      "answer": "rinse"
    },
    {
      "question": "love intensely",
      "answer": "adore"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of the salts of hydrobromic acid",
      "answer": "bromide"
    },
    {
      "question": "a band of warriors (originally a unit of a Roman Legion)  ",
      "answer": "cohort"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bundle of sticks and branches bound together  ",
      "answer": "fagot"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long (usually sleeveless) tunic of chain mail formerly worn as defensive armor  ",
      "answer": "hauberk"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of segregating or sequestering",
      "answer": "segregation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of trifling worth  ",
      "answer": "sixpenny"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or undergo a transition (from one state or system to another)",
      "answer": "transition"
    },
    {
      "question": "forbidden by law  ",
      "answer": "banned"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a benign manner",
      "answer": "benignly"
    },
    {
      "question": " situated in or directed toward the part of the body from which the tail arises",
      "answer": "caudal"
    },
    {
      "question": "break down",
      "answer": "decompose"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a noble manner",
      "answer": "nobly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman steward on an airplane  ",
      "answer": "stewardess"
    },
    {
      "question": "large oblong or roundish melon with a hard green rind and sweet watery red or occasionally yellowish pulp  ",
      "answer": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a loud resonant noise",
      "answer": "clangor"
    },
    {
      "question": "tableware implements for cutting and eating food  ",
      "answer": "cutlery"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who hunts wild birds for food  ",
      "answer": "fowler"
    },
    {
      "question": "important food fish on both sides of the Atlantic",
      "answer": "haddock"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of setting something on fire  ",
      "answer": "ignition"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who rescues you from harm or danger  ",
      "answer": "savior"
    },
    {
      "question": "an employee who mixes and serves alcoholic drinks at a bar  ",
      "answer": "bartender"
    },
    {
      "question": "the shell around the kernel of a nut  ",
      "answer": "nutshell"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who kills with poison  ",
      "answer": "poisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long flexible snout as of an elephant  ",
      "answer": "proboscis"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged like rays or radii",
      "answer": "radial"
    },
    {
      "question": "(biology) the structural adaptation of some body part for a particular function",
      "answer": "specialization"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing a sensation as of things crawling on your skin",
      "answer": "creepy"
    },
    {
      "question": "depriving of legal right",
      "answer": "disabling"
    },
    {
      "question": "an argument in which the participants are trying to gain some advantage  ",
      "answer": "sparring"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short stout club used primarily by policemen  ",
      "answer": "truncheon"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woodworker whose work involves making things by joining pieces of wood  ",
      "answer": "joiner"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by brief periods of violent wind or rain",
      "answer": "squally"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking a signature",
      "answer": "unsigned"
    },
    {
      "question": "nonchalantly unconcerned",
      "answer": "blase"
    },
    {
      "question": "mature male goose  ",
      "answer": "gander"
    },
    {
      "question": "a British unit of weight equivalent to 112 pounds  ",
      "answer": "hundredweight"
    },
    {
      "question": "attract more attention and praise than others",
      "answer": "outshine"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride a horse such that it springs and bounds forward  ",
      "answer": "prance"
    },
    {
      "question": "the entire range of skills or aptitudes or devices used in a particular field or occupation",
      "answer": "repertory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large sawing machine  ",
      "answer": "sawmill"
    },
    {
      "question": "with a sneer",
      "answer": "sneeringly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large wardrobe or cabinet",
      "answer": "armoire"
    },
    {
      "question": "the handle of a broom  ",
      "answer": "broomstick"
    },
    {
      "question": "make fertile or productive",
      "answer": "fertilize"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a humane manner",
      "answer": "humanely"
    },
    {
      "question": "boisterously and noisily aggressive",
      "answer": "obstreperous"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to Puritans or Puritanism  ",
      "answer": "puritanical"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman from your own country  ",
      "answer": "countrywoman"
    },
    {
      "question": "very tart red berry used for sauce or juice  ",
      "answer": "cranberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gabled extension built out from a sloping roof to accommodate a vertical window  ",
      "answer": "dormer"
    },
    {
      "question": "fat that exudes from meat and drips off while it is being roasted or fried  ",
      "answer": "drippings"
    },
    {
      "question": "a constantly changing medley of real or imagined images (as in a dream)  ",
      "answer": "phantasmagoria"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several small gregarious cetacean mammals having a blunt snout and many teeth  ",
      "answer": "porpoise"
    },
    {
      "question": "alternate the direction of motion of",
      "answer": "reciprocate"
    },
    {
      "question": "reclaimed wool fiber  ",
      "answer": "shoddy"
    },
    {
      "question": "disclosing information or giving evidence about another  ",
      "answer": "tattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "traveling (especially on foot)  ",
      "answer": "wayfaring"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a weird manner",
      "answer": "weirdly"
    },
    {
      "question": "displaying luxury and furnishing gratification to the senses",
      "answer": "epicurean"
    },
    {
      "question": "in this general vicinity",
      "answer": "hereabout"
    },
    {
      "question": "undergarment worn next to the skin and under the outer garments  ",
      "answer": "underwear"
    },
    {
      "question": "designed to be disposed of after use",
      "answer": "disposable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of sixty in counting order  ",
      "answer": "sixtieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "emitting or containing little or no smoke",
      "answer": "smokeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "the helmsman of a ship's boat or a racing crew  ",
      "answer": "coxswain"
    },
    {
      "question": "the gradual transformation of habitable land into desert",
      "answer": "desertification"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or resembling fibers especially fibers used in making cordage such as those of jute  ",
      "answer": "hempen"
    },
    {
      "question": "hulled corn with the bran and germ removed  ",
      "answer": "hominy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an animal trainer who tames wild animals  ",
      "answer": "tamer"
    },
    {
      "question": "domesticated llama with long silky fleece",
      "answer": "alpaca"
    },
    {
      "question": "fuse or cause to grow together  ",
      "answer": "coalesce"
    },
    {
      "question": "primly out of date",
      "answer": "dowdy"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various volatile flammable liquid hydrocarbon mixtures",
      "answer": "naphtha"
    },
    {
      "question": "short-legged flightless birds of cold southern especially Antarctic regions having webbed feet and wings modified as flippers  ",
      "answer": "penguin"
    },
    {
      "question": "express indirectly by an image, form, or model",
      "answer": "typify"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of persons) so unrefined as to be lacking in discrimination and sensibility  ",
      "answer": "crass"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wood of broad-leaved dicotyledonous trees (as distinguished from the wood of conifers)  ",
      "answer": "hardwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "push into action by pestering or annoying gently  ",
      "answer": "nudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "the revival of learning and culture  ",
      "answer": "rebirth"
    },
    {
      "question": "refuse to sponsor",
      "answer": "boycott"
    },
    {
      "question": "become systemic and spread throughout the body",
      "answer": "generalize"
    },
    {
      "question": "extraordinariness by virtue of being unexpected",
      "answer": "unexpectedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "edible tuberous root of various yam plants of the genus Dioscorea grown in the tropics world-wide for food  ",
      "answer": "yam"
    },
    {
      "question": "make attractive or lovable",
      "answer": "endear"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard as granite",
      "answer": "granitic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a verse line having six metrical feet  ",
      "answer": "hexameter"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit a putt",
      "answer": "putt"
    },
    {
      "question": "the incineration of a dead body  ",
      "answer": "cremation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a laborer who digs  ",
      "answer": "digger"
    },
    {
      "question": "the work of cutting down trees for timber  ",
      "answer": "logging"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artistic movement in 19th century France",
      "answer": "naturalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "selecting what seems best of various styles or ideas  ",
      "answer": "eclectic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the slender stem that supports the blade of a leaf  ",
      "answer": "petiole"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unforeseen or unexpected or surprising difficulty  ",
      "answer": "pitfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rod used to clean the barrel of a firearm  ",
      "answer": "ramrod"
    },
    {
      "question": "form a scab",
      "answer": "scab"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time of life between 60 and 70  ",
      "answer": "sixties"
    },
    {
      "question": "not reformed morally or spiritually",
      "answer": "unregenerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "prostitution of talents or offices or services for reward  ",
      "answer": "venality"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being dissimilar  ",
      "answer": "dissimilarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove with a flick (of the hand)  ",
      "answer": "flick"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being imminent and liable to happen soon  ",
      "answer": "imminence"
    },
    {
      "question": "murdering an infant  ",
      "answer": "infanticide"
    },
    {
      "question": "lift with a pitchfork",
      "answer": "pitchfork"
    },
    {
      "question": "a kitchen servant employed to do menial tasks (especially washing)  ",
      "answer": "scullion"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who transgresses",
      "answer": "transgressor"
    },
    {
      "question": "release from mental strain, tension, or formality",
      "answer": "unbend"
    },
    {
      "question": "impress greatly",
      "answer": "wow"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the heart",
      "answer": "cardiac"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lightweight triangular scarf worn by a woman  ",
      "answer": "fichu"
    },
    {
      "question": "a machine tool that polishes metal  ",
      "answer": "grinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "an optical toy in a tube",
      "answer": "kaleidoscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged with spaces between",
      "answer": "spaced"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tank or pool or bowl filled with water for keeping live fish and underwater animals  ",
      "answer": "aquarium"
    },
    {
      "question": "a class of verbs having the same inflectional forms  ",
      "answer": "conjugation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a collection of papers containing detailed information about a particular person or subject (usually a person's record)  ",
      "answer": "dossier"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or belonging to the family Equidae  ",
      "answer": "equine"
    },
    {
      "question": "fruit (especially peach) whose flesh does not adhere to the pit  ",
      "answer": "freestone"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being humble and unimportant  ",
      "answer": "humbleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being rigid and rigorously severe  ",
      "answer": "inflexibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "creating a sequence of instructions to enable the computer to do something  ",
      "answer": "programming"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone responsible for keeping records  ",
      "answer": "registrar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the unwritten lore (stories and proverbs and riddles and songs) of a culture  ",
      "answer": "folklore"
    },
    {
      "question": "make full of cavities, like a honeycomb  ",
      "answer": "honeycomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "unlawfulness by virtue of violating some legal statute  ",
      "answer": "illegality"
    },
    {
      "question": "make poor  ",
      "answer": "impoverish"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by bloodshed and carnage for both sides",
      "answer": "internecine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thin coagulable fluid (similar to plasma but) containing white blood cells (lymphocytes) and chyle",
      "answer": "lymph"
    },
    {
      "question": "meaningless ceremonies and flattery  ",
      "answer": "mummery"
    },
    {
      "question": "urge on",
      "answer": "prod"
    },
    {
      "question": "the offense of marrying someone while you have a living spouse from whom no valid divorce has occurred  ",
      "answer": "bigamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut through the backbone of an animal  ",
      "answer": "chine"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous tropical usually thorny evergreen trees of the genus Citrus having leathery evergreen leaves and widely cultivated for their juicy edible fruits having leathery aromatic rinds  ",
      "answer": "citrus"
    },
    {
      "question": "easy to believe on the basis of available evidence",
      "answer": "credibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most important point  ",
      "answer": "crux"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person skilled at symbolic logic  ",
      "answer": "logician"
    },
    {
      "question": "a manifest indication of the existence or presence or nature of some person or thing",
      "answer": "manifestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or involving dispute or controversy  ",
      "answer": "polemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "pertaining to giving directives or rules",
      "answer": "prescriptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "seizing property that belongs to someone else and holding it until profits pay the demand for which it was seized  ",
      "answer": "sequestration"
    },
    {
      "question": "the edge of a steep place  ",
      "answer": "brink"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shipwrecked person  ",
      "answer": "castaway"
    },
    {
      "question": "lizard of Africa and Madagascar able to change skin color and having a projectile tongue  ",
      "answer": "chameleon"
    },
    {
      "question": "make filigree, as with a precious metal  ",
      "answer": "filigree"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short pithy saying expressing a general truth  ",
      "answer": "gnome"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small amount of liquor added to a food or beverage  ",
      "answer": "lacing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a trite or obvious remark  ",
      "answer": "platitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "a collection of works (plays, songs, operas, ballets) that an artist or company can perform and do perform for short intervals on a regular schedule  ",
      "answer": "repertoire"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wooden board or platter on which food is served or carved  ",
      "answer": "trencher"
    },
    {
      "question": "lower in range than tenor and higher than bass",
      "answer": "baritone"
    },
    {
      "question": "squeeze together tightly",
      "answer": "clench"
    },
    {
      "question": "examine thoroughly",
      "answer": "grill"
    },
    {
      "question": "watch and direct",
      "answer": "oversee"
    },
    {
      "question": "pay back for some expense incurred",
      "answer": "reimburse"
    },
    {
      "question": "district consisting of the area on either side of a border or boundary of a country or an area",
      "answer": "borderland"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily irritated or annoyed",
      "answer": "cranky"
    },
    {
      "question": "atypically small",
      "answer": "dwarfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "made light by aerating, as with yeast or baking powder",
      "answer": "leavened"
    },
    {
      "question": "plundering during riots or in wartime  ",
      "answer": "looting"
    },
    {
      "question": "having unnatural mannerisms",
      "answer": "mannered"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loose and crumbling earthy deposit consisting mainly of calcite or dolomite",
      "answer": "marl"
    },
    {
      "question": "a humanist specializing in classical scholarship  ",
      "answer": "philologist"
    },
    {
      "question": "having an indicated pole (as the distinction between positive and negative electric charges)",
      "answer": "polarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group of three men responsible for public administration or civil authority  ",
      "answer": "triumvirate"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking information or instruction",
      "answer": "uninstructed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the decade from 1940 to 1949  ",
      "answer": "forties"
    },
    {
      "question": "desire strongly or persistently  ",
      "answer": "hanker"
    },
    {
      "question": "faithful and true",
      "answer": "leal"
    },
    {
      "question": "nocturnal arboreal marsupial having a naked prehensile tail found from southern North America to northern South America  ",
      "answer": "opossum"
    },
    {
      "question": "without warning or announcement",
      "answer": "unannounced"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) an abnormal outgrowth or enlargement of some part of the body  ",
      "answer": "excrescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "tallest living quadruped",
      "answer": "giraffe"
    },
    {
      "question": "not fit for habitation  ",
      "answer": "uninhabitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who speaks disrespectfully of sacred things  ",
      "answer": "blasphemer"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving inferences from general principles  ",
      "answer": "deductive"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a softened tone",
      "answer": "hushed"
    },
    {
      "question": "do a somersault  ",
      "answer": "somersault"
    },
    {
      "question": "given to excess in consumption of especially food or drink",
      "answer": "gluttonous"
    },
    {
      "question": "make mad",
      "answer": "madden"
    },
    {
      "question": "white sheep originating in Spain and producing a heavy fleece of exceptional quality  ",
      "answer": "merino"
    },
    {
      "question": "protective secretion of the mucus membranes",
      "answer": "mucus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flexible cap on a baby's feeding bottle or pacifier  ",
      "answer": "nipple"
    },
    {
      "question": "pod of the peanut vine containing usually 2 nuts or seeds",
      "answer": "peanut"
    },
    {
      "question": "properties acquired during a person's formative years  ",
      "answer": "upbringing"
    },
    {
      "question": "(classical mythology) the food and drink of the gods",
      "answer": "ambrosia"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or concerned with the science of anthropology",
      "answer": "anthropological"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female bartender  ",
      "answer": "barmaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strap from the back of a saddle passing under the horse's tail",
      "answer": "crupper"
    },
    {
      "question": "go mad, go crazy",
      "answer": "flip"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or characteristic of non-Jewish peoples  ",
      "answer": "gentile"
    },
    {
      "question": "inflexibly entrenched and unchangeable",
      "answer": "ironclad"
    },
    {
      "question": "government that is inefficient or dishonest  ",
      "answer": "misgovernment"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who jeers or mocks or treats something with contempt or calls out in derision  ",
      "answer": "scoffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the disturbance of a systematic arrangement causing disorder and confusion",
      "answer": "disorganization"
    },
    {
      "question": "deliberate discourtesy  ",
      "answer": "incivility"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who delivers milk  ",
      "answer": "milkman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the word class that can serve as the subject or object of a verb, the object of a preposition, or in apposition  ",
      "answer": "noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Roman Catholic Church) a diplomatic representative of the Pope having ambassadorial status  ",
      "answer": "nuncio"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who sows  ",
      "answer": "sower"
    },
    {
      "question": "pick consisting of a small strip of wood or plastic",
      "answer": "toothpick"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who was versed in the practice of alchemy and who sought an elixir of life and a panacea and an alkahest and the philosopher's stone  ",
      "answer": "alchemist"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or resembling a bureaucrat or bureaucracy",
      "answer": "bureaucratic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the relation between causes and effects  ",
      "answer": "causality"
    },
    {
      "question": "something desired as a necessity",
      "answer": "desideratum"
    },
    {
      "question": "to an inexpressible degree",
      "answer": "ineffably"
    },
    {
      "question": "fore-and-aft sail set on the mizzenmast  ",
      "answer": "mizzen"
    },
    {
      "question": "not sensible about practical matters",
      "answer": "quixotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "(music) a notation written at the beginning or end of a passage that is to be repeated  ",
      "answer": "segno"
    },
    {
      "question": "the calculated use of violence (or the threat of violence) against civilians in order to attain goals that are political or religious or ideological in nature",
      "answer": "terrorism"
    },
    {
      "question": "of interest at the present time",
      "answer": "topical"
    },
    {
      "question": "overabundance of words  ",
      "answer": "verbiage"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various edible tropical marine gastropods of the genus Strombus having a brightly-colored spiral shell with large outer lip  ",
      "answer": "conch"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward the shore",
      "answer": "inshore"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter a high-pitched cry, as of seagulls  ",
      "answer": "mew"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow faster than  ",
      "answer": "outgrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used especially of meat) cured in brine  ",
      "answer": "corned"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who hops",
      "answer": "hopper"
    },
    {
      "question": "of qualities that are spread throughout something",
      "answer": "immanent"
    },
    {
      "question": "lens for correcting defective vision in one eye",
      "answer": "monocle"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a summary (of)  ",
      "answer": "precis"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of propelling  ",
      "answer": "propulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "gregarious birds native to the Old World  ",
      "answer": "starling"
    },
    {
      "question": "not given to open expression of emotion  ",
      "answer": "undemonstrative"
    },
    {
      "question": "pH values below 7  ",
      "answer": "acidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "an incompetent or clumsy person",
      "answer": "duffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the practice of scrupulous adherence to prescribed or external forms  ",
      "answer": "formalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "having little desire for success or achievement  ",
      "answer": "unambitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "small donkey used as a pack animal  ",
      "answer": "burro"
    },
    {
      "question": "the forestay that braces the mainmast  ",
      "answer": "mainstay"
    },
    {
      "question": "inflammation of the nose and throat with increased production of mucus  ",
      "answer": "catarrh"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small boat of shallow draft with cross thwarts for seats and rowlocks for oars with which it is propelled  ",
      "answer": "dinghy"
    },
    {
      "question": "produced by inbreeding  ",
      "answer": "inbred"
    },
    {
      "question": "nonsense that is simply incoherent and unintelligible  ",
      "answer": "incoherence"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) the phase in the development of an infection between the time a pathogen enters the body and the time the first symptoms appear  ",
      "answer": "incubation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of master  ",
      "answer": "mastership"
    },
    {
      "question": "bottom dwelling marine warm water fishes with two barbels on the chin  ",
      "answer": "mullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "create anew",
      "answer": "recreate"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggesting human characteristics for animals or inanimate things  ",
      "answer": "anthropomorphic"
    },
    {
      "question": "old fashioned airplane",
      "answer": "biplane"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous low-growing plants of the genus Crocus having slender grasslike leaves and white or yellow or purple flowers",
      "answer": "crocus"
    },
    {
      "question": "negligent of neatness especially in dress and person",
      "answer": "frowsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ancient Greece) a hymn of praise (especially one sung in ancient Greece to invoke or thank a deity)  ",
      "answer": "paean"
    },
    {
      "question": "an official responsible for control and supervision of a particular activity or area of public interest  ",
      "answer": "regulator"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of seventy in counting order  ",
      "answer": "seventieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of weather) wet by periods of rain",
      "answer": "showery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a job involving drudgery and confinement  ",
      "answer": "treadmill"
    },
    {
      "question": "not just or fair",
      "answer": "wrongful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musician who adapts a composition for particular voices or instruments or for another style of performance  ",
      "answer": "arranger"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a forlorn manner",
      "answer": "forlornly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the yield of fruit",
      "answer": "fruitage"
    },
    {
      "question": "an optical instrument that projects an enlarged image onto a screen  ",
      "answer": "projector"
    },
    {
      "question": "not musical in nature",
      "answer": "unmusical"
    },
    {
      "question": "protected with battlements or parapets with indentations or embrasures for shooting through  ",
      "answer": "battlemented"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unmarried woman who attends the bride at a wedding  ",
      "answer": "bridesmaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "an infection larger than a boil and with several openings for discharge of pus  ",
      "answer": "carbuncle"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unborn or unhatched vertebrate in the later stages of development showing the main recognizable features of the mature animal  ",
      "answer": "fetus"
    },
    {
      "question": "the drinking of large mouthfuls rapidly  ",
      "answer": "gulping"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impolite act or expression  ",
      "answer": "indelicacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "slender-bodied semiaquatic mammal having partially webbed feet",
      "answer": "mink"
    },
    {
      "question": "not having a point especially a sharp point",
      "answer": "pointless"
    },
    {
      "question": "outer surface of an area or a body  ",
      "answer": "superficies"
    },
    {
      "question": "a garment (or part of a garment) designed for or relating to trousers",
      "answer": "trouser"
    },
    {
      "question": "pull or lift up with or as if with a winch",
      "answer": "winch"
    },
    {
      "question": "skill in carving or fashioning objects from wood  ",
      "answer": "woodcraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a mature manner",
      "answer": "maturely"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a measurable degree",
      "answer": "measurably"
    },
    {
      "question": "putting seeds or young plants in the ground to grow",
      "answer": "planting"
    },
    {
      "question": "directed or moving toward the rear",
      "answer": "rearward"
    },
    {
      "question": "the belief in government by divine guidance  ",
      "answer": "theocracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "jostling with the elbows",
      "answer": "elbowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no hair or fur",
      "answer": "hairless"
    },
    {
      "question": "jump a hurdle  ",
      "answer": "hurdle"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of sin  ",
      "answer": "impeccable"
    },
    {
      "question": "not conclusive",
      "answer": "inconclusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long dress worn by women  ",
      "answer": "kirtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "of something having the color of copper  ",
      "answer": "coppery"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characterized by fever",
      "answer": "febrile"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a physically fierce manner",
      "answer": "ferociously"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several small spiny trees or shrubs of the genus Prosopis having small flowers in axillary cylindrical spikes followed by large pods rich in sugar  ",
      "answer": "mesquite"
    },
    {
      "question": "not debased",
      "answer": "uncorrupted"
    },
    {
      "question": "an auxiliary activity  ",
      "answer": "avocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of creating something (a medicine or drink or soup etc.) by compounding or mixing a variety of components  ",
      "answer": "confection"
    },
    {
      "question": "by custom",
      "answer": "customarily"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold with difficulty and balance insecurely",
      "answer": "juggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "ribald humor  ",
      "answer": "ribaldry"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing lack of love for your country  ",
      "answer": "unpatriotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "early spring flower common in British isles having fragrant yellow or sometimes purple flowers  ",
      "answer": "cowslip"
    },
    {
      "question": "an establishment on the waterfront where vessels are built or fitted out or repaired  ",
      "answer": "dockyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "the status of a father  ",
      "answer": "fatherhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the cultivation of plants  ",
      "answer": "horticultural"
    },
    {
      "question": "a plant that is found in an area where it had not been recorded previously  ",
      "answer": "neophyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an obsequious manner",
      "answer": "obsequiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several low-growing palms with fan-shaped leaves  ",
      "answer": "palmetto"
    },
    {
      "question": "one section of a lyric poem or choral ode in classical Greek drama  ",
      "answer": "strophe"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of vowels or syllables) pronounced with little or no stress",
      "answer": "unaccented"
    },
    {
      "question": "as an adjective",
      "answer": "adjectively"
    },
    {
      "question": "a breed of stocky medium-sized short-haired dog with a brindled coat and square-jawed muzzle developed in Germany  ",
      "answer": "boxer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a partition that divides a ship or plane into compartments  ",
      "answer": "bulkhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "bob forward and under so as to feed off the bottom of a body of water",
      "answer": "dabble"
    },
    {
      "question": "become worse or disintegrate",
      "answer": "deteriorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a dry laconic manner",
      "answer": "laconically"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who releases people from captivity or bondage  ",
      "answer": "liberator"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who takes part in an activity  ",
      "answer": "participant"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a heavy ponderous manner",
      "answer": "ponderously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the thick white fluid containing spermatozoa that is ejaculated by the male genital tract  ",
      "answer": "semen"
    },
    {
      "question": "an expression of disappointment or irritation  ",
      "answer": "shucks"
    },
    {
      "question": "favoring or practicing capitalism  ",
      "answer": "capitalistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sharp abrupt noise as if two objects hit together",
      "answer": "clack"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman hunter  ",
      "answer": "huntress"
    },
    {
      "question": "state of elementary or undifferentiated consciousness",
      "answer": "awareness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a polysaccharide that is the chief constituent of all plant tissues and fibers  ",
      "answer": "cellulose"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mixed drink containing champagne and orange juice  ",
      "answer": "mimosa"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being capable of mutation  ",
      "answer": "mutability"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to make sober or more serious",
      "answer": "sobering"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being strong and resolute  ",
      "answer": "stoutness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shed for storing firewood or garden tools  ",
      "answer": "woodshed"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to breathing with a whistling sound  ",
      "answer": "asthmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an earthen rampart  ",
      "answer": "earthwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "bathe with warm water or medicated lotions",
      "answer": "foment"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inability to read  ",
      "answer": "illiteracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "organized as or forming an institution",
      "answer": "institutional"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or characterized by or consisting of one syllable  ",
      "answer": "monosyllabic"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who adheres to strict religious principles",
      "answer": "puritan"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman's drawstring handbag",
      "answer": "reticule"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a romantic manner",
      "answer": "romantically"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnished with funds",
      "answer": "funded"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an irreverent or profane manner",
      "answer": "profanely"
    },
    {
      "question": "being disposed to do something",
      "answer": "proneness"
    },
    {
      "question": "take the burden off",
      "answer": "unburden"
    },
    {
      "question": "irregular and infrequent or difficult evacuation of the bowels",
      "answer": "constipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "monstrous sea creature symbolizing evil in the Old Testament  ",
      "answer": "leviathan"
    },
    {
      "question": "make imperfect",
      "answer": "mar"
    },
    {
      "question": "slender tower with balconies  ",
      "answer": "minaret"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling or containing or formed by the accumulation of sediment",
      "answer": "sedimentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of subtracting (removing a part from the whole)",
      "answer": "subtraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "the railing around the stern of a ship  ",
      "answer": "taffrail"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tense manner",
      "answer": "tensely"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small outdoor fire for warmth or cooking (as at a camp)  ",
      "answer": "campfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of sounding harmonious  ",
      "answer": "consonance"
    },
    {
      "question": "prevent the occurrence of",
      "answer": "debar"
    },
    {
      "question": "print incorrectly  ",
      "answer": "misprint"
    },
    {
      "question": "(from a combination of MOdulate and DEModulate) electronic equipment consisting of a device used to connect computers by a telephone line  ",
      "answer": "modem"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wig for men that was fashionable in the 17th and 18th centuries  ",
      "answer": "periwig"
    },
    {
      "question": "repetition of an act needlessly  ",
      "answer": "redundancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flag having three colored stripes (especially the French flag)  ",
      "answer": "tricolor"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a mine or oil well) drilled speculatively in an area not known to be productive",
      "answer": "wildcat"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a flagrant manner",
      "answer": "flagrantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "with humor",
      "answer": "jocosely"
    },
    {
      "question": "cheap clothing (as formerly issued to sailors in Britain)  ",
      "answer": "slops"
    },
    {
      "question": "a second-year undergraduate  ",
      "answer": "sophomore"
    },
    {
      "question": "give off (water) through the skin  ",
      "answer": "transpire"
    },
    {
      "question": "(electronics) the act of increasing voltage or power or current  ",
      "answer": "amplification"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small and delicately worked piece  ",
      "answer": "bijou"
    },
    {
      "question": "the inanimate property of something that has died  ",
      "answer": "deadness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reference work (often in several volumes) containing articles on various topics (often arranged in alphabetical order) dealing with the entire range of human knowledge or with some particular specialty  ",
      "answer": "encyclopedia"
    },
    {
      "question": "the origin of some development",
      "answer": "germination"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of acting suddenly on impulse without reflection  ",
      "answer": "impulsiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or produced by lymph  ",
      "answer": "lymphatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "confused and not coherent",
      "answer": "fuzzy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of cutting into an edge with toothlike notches or angular incisions  ",
      "answer": "indentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the amount that can be bought for a penny  ",
      "answer": "pennyworth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ski run densely packed with snow  ",
      "answer": "piste"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or shaped like a quadrangle  ",
      "answer": "quadrangular"
    },
    {
      "question": "elimination of superfluous details  ",
      "answer": "simplification"
    },
    {
      "question": "the placing of seeds in damp sand or sawdust or peat moss in order to preserve them or promote germination  ",
      "answer": "stratification"
    },
    {
      "question": "spanning or extending throughout the entire world",
      "answer": "worldwide"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several fleet black-and-white striped African equines  ",
      "answer": "zebra"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various resins or oleoresins  ",
      "answer": "anime"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loose fitting jacket",
      "answer": "banyan"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of forcing out someone or something",
      "answer": "ejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inaudible manner",
      "answer": "inaudibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who dislikes people in general  ",
      "answer": "misanthrope"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter in a grating voice  ",
      "answer": "rasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state exercising a degree of dominion over a dependent state especially in its foreign affairs  ",
      "answer": "suzerain"
    },
    {
      "question": "of equal importance, rank, or degree  ",
      "answer": "coordinate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making slaves of your captives  ",
      "answer": "enslavement"
    },
    {
      "question": "arouse hostility or indifference in where there had formerly been love, affection, or friendliness",
      "answer": "estrange"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of having little body fat  ",
      "answer": "leanness"
    },
    {
      "question": "improve the morals of  ",
      "answer": "moralize"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inexperienced person (especially someone inexperienced in outdoor living)  ",
      "answer": "tenderfoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "the regulation of occurrence, pace, or coordination to achieve a desired effect (as in music, theater, athletics, mechanics)  ",
      "answer": "timing"
    },
    {
      "question": "eaten away as by acid or oxidation  ",
      "answer": "corroded"
    },
    {
      "question": "abject or cringing submissiveness  ",
      "answer": "obsequiousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "examine someone's knowledge of something",
      "answer": "quiz"
    },
    {
      "question": "speak or recite rapidly or in a rolling voice  ",
      "answer": "troll"
    },
    {
      "question": "engraving consisting of a block of wood with a design cut into it",
      "answer": "woodcut"
    },
    {
      "question": "supplied with a dower or dowry  ",
      "answer": "dowered"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk a long way, as for pleasure or physical exercise",
      "answer": "hike"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose business involves importing goods from outside (especially from a foreign country)  ",
      "answer": "importer"
    },
    {
      "question": "in jest",
      "answer": "jokingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with blood",
      "answer": "bloodstained"
    },
    {
      "question": "put into a new order or arrangement",
      "answer": "rearrange"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking knowledge gained by study often in a particular field",
      "answer": "unstudied"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being beautiful and delicate in appearance",
      "answer": "daintiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an adventurous manner",
      "answer": "daringly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of detonating an explosive  ",
      "answer": "detonation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to ethnology",
      "answer": "ethnological"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpredictably difficult in operation",
      "answer": "fractious"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or involving incest  ",
      "answer": "incestuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "articulate in a very careful and rhythmic way  ",
      "answer": "lilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "dance a polka  ",
      "answer": "polka"
    },
    {
      "question": "wash in suds  ",
      "answer": "suds"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an ungrateful manner  ",
      "answer": "ungratefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an ecstatic manner",
      "answer": "ecstatically"
    },
    {
      "question": "register formally as a participant or member",
      "answer": "enroll"
    },
    {
      "question": "plot of land belonging to an English parish church or an ecclesiastical office  ",
      "answer": "glebe"
    },
    {
      "question": "agile slender-bodied arboreal mustelids somewhat larger than weasels  ",
      "answer": "marten"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a nose (either literal or metaphoric) especially of a specified kind  ",
      "answer": "nosed"
    },
    {
      "question": "brilliantly clever",
      "answer": "scintillating"
    },
    {
      "question": "make undue claims to having  ",
      "answer": "arrogate"
    },
    {
      "question": "relatively small compact tawny-brown heron with nocturnal habits and a booming cry",
      "answer": "bittern"
    },
    {
      "question": "an order that after a specific time certain activities (as being outside on the streets) are prohibited  ",
      "answer": "curfew"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of or giving praise",
      "answer": "laudatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "being on the point of death",
      "answer": "moribund"
    },
    {
      "question": "arouse again",
      "answer": "rekindle"
    },
    {
      "question": "move stealthily",
      "answer": "skulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sour manner",
      "answer": "sourly"
    },
    {
      "question": "something of small importance  ",
      "answer": "triviality"
    },
    {
      "question": "the pleasure of remembering some pleasant event",
      "answer": "afterglow"
    },
    {
      "question": "not straightforward or candid",
      "answer": "disingenuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "right of inheritance belongs exclusively to the eldest son  ",
      "answer": "primogeniture"
    },
    {
      "question": "large metallic blue-green beetle that preys on caterpillars",
      "answer": "searcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mechanical device for stoking a furnace  ",
      "answer": "stoker"
    },
    {
      "question": "not cooked  ",
      "answer": "uncooked"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the direction against a stream's current  ",
      "answer": "upstream"
    },
    {
      "question": "the title of a baron  ",
      "answer": "baronetcy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being painful",
      "answer": "painfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the amount by which something shrinks  ",
      "answer": "shrinkage"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or resembling a shrub  ",
      "answer": "shrubby"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tool for rounding corners or edges  ",
      "answer": "rounder"
    },
    {
      "question": "made infertile  ",
      "answer": "sterilized"
    },
    {
      "question": "not expressing or given to expressing the truth",
      "answer": "untruthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man who raises (or tends) cattle  ",
      "answer": "cattleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of a curate  ",
      "answer": "curacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "thick-walled muscular pouch below the crop in many birds and reptiles for grinding food  ",
      "answer": "gizzard"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time between two reigns, governments, etc.  ",
      "answer": "interregnum"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of an attractively thin person  ",
      "answer": "slenderness"
    },
    {
      "question": "an alkaloid plant toxin extracted chiefly from nux vomica",
      "answer": "strychnine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large brownish European flatfish  ",
      "answer": "turbot"
    },
    {
      "question": "not chaste",
      "answer": "unchaste"
    },
    {
      "question": "a contrived or fantastic idea",
      "answer": "figment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a protein substance that remains when starch is removed from cereal grains",
      "answer": "gluten"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of or capable of or having a tendency toward killing another human being ",
      "answer": "homicidal"
    },
    {
      "question": "not following logically as a consequence  ",
      "answer": "inconsequential"
    },
    {
      "question": "cloth treated on one side with a drying oil or synthetic resin  ",
      "answer": "oilcloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various metallic-looking sulfides (of which pyrite is the commonest)  ",
      "answer": "pyrites"
    },
    {
      "question": "a consonant characterized by a hissing sound (like s or sh)  ",
      "answer": "sibilant"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who habitually doubts accepted beliefs  ",
      "answer": "skeptic"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw snowballs at  ",
      "answer": "snowball"
    },
    {
      "question": "not wounded  ",
      "answer": "unwounded"
    },
    {
      "question": "having been demonstrated or verified beyond doubt  ",
      "answer": "demonstrated"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ray of moonlight  ",
      "answer": "moonbeam"
    },
    {
      "question": "any shrub of the genus Rhododendron: evergreen shrubs or small shrubby trees having leathery leaves and showy clusters of campanulate (bell-shaped) flowers  ",
      "answer": "rhododendron"
    },
    {
      "question": "talk at great length about something of one's interest  ",
      "answer": "descant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bed of earth covered with glass and heated by rotting manure to promote the growth of plants  ",
      "answer": "hotbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of having no practical use  ",
      "answer": "inutility"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a command of or composed in many languages",
      "answer": "polyglot"
    },
    {
      "question": "according with conscience or morality  ",
      "answer": "rightness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being topologically uneven",
      "answer": "ruggedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "brown-speckled European lark noted for singing while hovering at a great height  ",
      "answer": "skylark"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conveyance that transports passengers or freight in carriers suspended from cables and supported by a series of towers  ",
      "answer": "tramway"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit a ball in such a way so as to make it go a short distance  ",
      "answer": "bunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a band or collar that holds an individual stone in a jewelry setting  ",
      "answer": "collet"
    },
    {
      "question": "enter as debit  ",
      "answer": "debit"
    },
    {
      "question": "gown (especially ceremonial garments) worn by the clergy  ",
      "answer": "vestment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a food fish of the Atlantic waters of Europe resembling the cod",
      "answer": "whiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "live like a buccaneer  ",
      "answer": "buccaneer"
    },
    {
      "question": "large deep dish in which food can be cooked and served  ",
      "answer": "casserole"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vociferous manner",
      "answer": "vociferously"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a willful manner",
      "answer": "willfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "an area of ground used for some particular purpose (such as building or farming)",
      "answer": "acreage"
    },
    {
      "question": "show disapproval by discouraging",
      "answer": "discountenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "the same distance apart at every point  ",
      "answer": "equidistant"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inconvenient manner",
      "answer": "inconveniently"
    },
    {
      "question": "an authoritative declaration  ",
      "answer": "pronouncement"
    },
    {
      "question": "with suavity",
      "answer": "suavely"
    },
    {
      "question": "a measuring instrument or device for keeping time  ",
      "answer": "timepiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "terminate debate by calling for a vote",
      "answer": "closure"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical form consisting of a theme repeated a fifth above or a fourth below its first statement  ",
      "answer": "fugue"
    },
    {
      "question": "talk in a dogmatic and pompous manner",
      "answer": "pontificate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the pace of things that move relatively slowly",
      "answer": "sluggishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being sober and not intoxicated by alcohol  ",
      "answer": "soberness"
    },
    {
      "question": "uneven by virtue of having wrinkles or waves  ",
      "answer": "crinkled"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a fanciful manner",
      "answer": "fancifully"
    },
    {
      "question": "large stinging paper wasp  ",
      "answer": "hornet"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of military officers) appointed from enlisted personnel  ",
      "answer": "noncommissioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "make too high an estimate of",
      "answer": "overestimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of lacking strength or power",
      "answer": "powerlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "put a law into effect by formal declaration  ",
      "answer": "promulgate"
    },
    {
      "question": "feed pigs  ",
      "answer": "slop"
    },
    {
      "question": "expressing reproof or reproach especially as a corrective  ",
      "answer": "admonitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "not slowed or prevented",
      "answer": "unimpeded"
    },
    {
      "question": "a constant number that serves as a measure of some property or characteristic  ",
      "answer": "coefficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "with condescension",
      "answer": "condescendingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the pivot about which a lever turns  ",
      "answer": "fulcrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "changing the ground level to a smooth horizontal or gently sloping surface  ",
      "answer": "grading"
    },
    {
      "question": "asceticism as a form of religious life",
      "answer": "monasticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "the decade from 1930 to 1939  ",
      "answer": "thirties"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being blank",
      "answer": "blankness"
    },
    {
      "question": "with diplomacy",
      "answer": "diplomatically"
    },
    {
      "question": "clinic where medicine and medical supplies are dispensed  ",
      "answer": "dispensary"
    },
    {
      "question": "limited to or caring only about yourself and your own needs  ",
      "answer": "egoistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "rescue equipment consisting of a device that fills with air and retards your fall  ",
      "answer": "parachute"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several public officials of ancient Rome (usually in charge of finance and administration)  ",
      "answer": "quaestor"
    },
    {
      "question": "with reverence",
      "answer": "reverentially"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking variety  ",
      "answer": "unvaried"
    },
    {
      "question": "a noisy or scolding or domineering woman  ",
      "answer": "virago"
    },
    {
      "question": "revoke formally  ",
      "answer": "abrogate"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a common axis  ",
      "answer": "coaxial"
    },
    {
      "question": "rise to, or form, a summit",
      "answer": "culminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "kill without legal sanction",
      "answer": "lynch"
    },
    {
      "question": "permanent canopy over an entrance of a hotel etc.  ",
      "answer": "marquee"
    },
    {
      "question": "beyond the regular time",
      "answer": "overtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "cultivate, tend, and cut back the growth of",
      "answer": "snip"
    },
    {
      "question": "not aware or knowing",
      "answer": "unwitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being regulated",
      "answer": "adjustable"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked with stripes or bands  ",
      "answer": "barred"
    },
    {
      "question": "hollow or grooved tooth of a venomous snake",
      "answer": "fang"
    },
    {
      "question": "reptilian creature supposed to live in fire  ",
      "answer": "salamander"
    },
    {
      "question": "not starry",
      "answer": "starless"
    },
    {
      "question": "adhering or confined to a particular sect or denomination",
      "answer": "denominational"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lightweight waterproof (usually rubberized) fabric  ",
      "answer": "mackintosh"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by soft sounds",
      "answer": "murmurous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a parish  ",
      "answer": "parishioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wandering or disorderly grouping (of things or persons)",
      "answer": "straggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tart manner",
      "answer": "tartly"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various small short-necked dabbling river ducks of Europe and America  ",
      "answer": "teal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a craftsman who upholsters furniture  ",
      "answer": "upholsterer"
    },
    {
      "question": "rapidity of movement",
      "answer": "fleetness"
    },
    {
      "question": "make furious  ",
      "answer": "infuriate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chief of a North American tribe or confederation (especially an Algonquian chief)  ",
      "answer": "sachem"
    },
    {
      "question": "alter the nature of (elements)  ",
      "answer": "transmute"
    },
    {
      "question": "protected from harm or loss  ",
      "answer": "conserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "charge falsely or with malicious intent",
      "answer": "defame"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the external sex organs",
      "answer": "genital"
    },
    {
      "question": "a metric unit of length equal to 1000 meters (or 0.621371 miles)  ",
      "answer": "kilometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "heated beyond a safe or desirable point",
      "answer": "overheated"
    },
    {
      "question": "drive a skewer through",
      "answer": "skewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being steady and unfailing",
      "answer": "sureness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of becoming formally connected or joined",
      "answer": "affiliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook on a griddle",
      "answer": "griddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "be larger in number  ",
      "answer": "outnumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "protective covering consisting, for example, of a layer of boards applied to the studs and joists of a building to strengthen it and serve as a foundation for a weatherproof exterior  ",
      "answer": "sheathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various naturally occurring impure mixtures of hydrocarbons  ",
      "answer": "bitumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "the removal of covering  ",
      "answer": "denudation"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a glaring manner",
      "answer": "glaringly"
    },
    {
      "question": "anything from which something can be hung  ",
      "answer": "hanger"
    },
    {
      "question": "affect with, or as if with, jaundice  ",
      "answer": "jaundice"
    },
    {
      "question": "a colonnade surrounding a building or enclosing a court  ",
      "answer": "peristyle"
    },
    {
      "question": "seven times",
      "answer": "sevenfold"
    },
    {
      "question": "a usually cotton fabric with a short pile imitating velvet  ",
      "answer": "velveteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "the use or application of an accent",
      "answer": "accentuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bow fixed transversely on a wooden stock grooved to direct the arrow (quarrel)  ",
      "answer": "crossbow"
    },
    {
      "question": "far removed mentally",
      "answer": "faraway"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a low continuous sound",
      "answer": "hum"
    },
    {
      "question": "total lack of meaning or ideas  ",
      "answer": "inanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "an agent in the buying and selling of stocks and bonds  ",
      "answer": "stockbroker"
    },
    {
      "question": "not digested",
      "answer": "undigested"
    },
    {
      "question": "without grace",
      "answer": "ungraciously"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no intellectual or emotional or spiritual excitement",
      "answer": "uninspired"
    },
    {
      "question": "the final judgment in a legal proceeding",
      "answer": "adjudication"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing gold",
      "answer": "auriferous"
    },
    {
      "question": "collapse like a concertina  ",
      "answer": "concertina"
    },
    {
      "question": "a postulated sequence of possible events",
      "answer": "scenario"
    },
    {
      "question": "a temporary resident  ",
      "answer": "sojourner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a painful injury to a joint caused by a sudden wrenching of its ligaments  ",
      "answer": "sprain"
    },
    {
      "question": "favoring one person or side over another",
      "answer": "biased"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nonmagnetic housing for a ship's compass (usually in front of the helm)  ",
      "answer": "binnacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "alcoholic liquor flavored with bitter herbs and roots  ",
      "answer": "bitters"
    },
    {
      "question": "light rowboat for use in racing or for transporting goods and passengers in inland waters and harbors  ",
      "answer": "wherry"
    },
    {
      "question": "moistening a roast as it is cooking  ",
      "answer": "basting"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ore of boron consisting of hydrated sodium borate",
      "answer": "borax"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a strong pink to yellowish-pink color  ",
      "answer": "coral"
    },
    {
      "question": "with regard to emotions",
      "answer": "emotionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "nonpasserine large-headed bird with a short tail and long sharp bill",
      "answer": "kingfisher"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook in a marinade",
      "answer": "souse"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes or repairs watches  ",
      "answer": "watchmaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bell tower",
      "answer": "campanile"
    },
    {
      "question": "in violation of the law",
      "answer": "criminally"
    },
    {
      "question": "a divided skirt  ",
      "answer": "culotte"
    },
    {
      "question": "an extractor consisting of a pair of pincers used in medical treatment (especially for the delivery of babies)  ",
      "answer": "forceps"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inverse or contrary manner",
      "answer": "inversely"
    },
    {
      "question": "a light silver-white ductile bivalent metallic element",
      "answer": "magnesium"
    },
    {
      "question": "rule against",
      "answer": "overrule"
    },
    {
      "question": "small crested arboreal lizard able to run on its hind legs",
      "answer": "basilisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "settle as colonists or establish a colony (in)",
      "answer": "colonize"
    },
    {
      "question": "shaped like a dish or pan  ",
      "answer": "dished"
    },
    {
      "question": "the interior part of a country  ",
      "answer": "midland"
    },
    {
      "question": "be apathetic, gloomy, or dazed  ",
      "answer": "mope"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of reviving a person and returning them to consciousness",
      "answer": "resuscitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male slave  ",
      "answer": "bondman"
    },
    {
      "question": "freed from enchantment  ",
      "answer": "disenchanted"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an exultant manner",
      "answer": "exultantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "having decorative ruffles or frills  ",
      "answer": "frilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "rapid and indistinct speech  ",
      "answer": "jabber"
    },
    {
      "question": "by means of symbols",
      "answer": "symbolically"
    },
    {
      "question": "the forceful expulsion of something from inside",
      "answer": "belching"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large round seedless or seeded fruit with a texture like bread",
      "answer": "breadfruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being balanced  ",
      "answer": "evenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "stable gear consisting of any part of a harness that fits about the horse's head  ",
      "answer": "headgear"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking mirth  ",
      "answer": "mirthless"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by complete cowardliness  ",
      "answer": "poltroon"
    },
    {
      "question": "not burdened with difficulties or responsibilities",
      "answer": "unburdened"
    },
    {
      "question": "interlace to form wattle  ",
      "answer": "wattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who commits adultery or fornication  ",
      "answer": "adulterer"
    },
    {
      "question": "connecting or tending to connect",
      "answer": "connective"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to deter",
      "answer": "deterrent"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a manner or to an extent that is well known",
      "answer": "famously"
    },
    {
      "question": "whip with a whip intended for horses  ",
      "answer": "horsewhip"
    },
    {
      "question": "attack as false or wrong  ",
      "answer": "impugn"
    },
    {
      "question": "the moment of most intense pleasure in sexual intercourse  ",
      "answer": "orgasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in South Africa",
      "answer": "rand"
    },
    {
      "question": "a temperament that is perturbed and lacking in composure  ",
      "answer": "discomposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "based on or belonging to etymology",
      "answer": "etymological"
    },
    {
      "question": "ostentatious or vainglorious or extravagant or melodramatic conduct",
      "answer": "heroics"
    },
    {
      "question": "prohibited by official rules",
      "answer": "ineligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "(vertebrates) one of usually two organs that produce ova and secrete estrogen and progesterone  ",
      "answer": "ovary"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sluggish manner",
      "answer": "sluggishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hand tool for boring holes  ",
      "answer": "auger"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process whereby water particles become visible in the sky  ",
      "answer": "clouding"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a flirtatious manner",
      "answer": "coquettishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical composition of a free form usually incorporating several familiar themes  ",
      "answer": "fantasia"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of behaving in ways considered typical for women  ",
      "answer": "femininity"
    },
    {
      "question": "without discretion or wisdom or self-restraint",
      "answer": "indiscreetly"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to discourage (especially of prices)",
      "answer": "prohibitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "from the subconscious mind",
      "answer": "subconsciously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of adulterating (especially the illicit substitution of one substance for another)  ",
      "answer": "adulteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "an upholstered bench  ",
      "answer": "banquette"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most commonly used illicit drug",
      "answer": "cannabis"
    },
    {
      "question": "lose confidence or hope",
      "answer": "despond"
    },
    {
      "question": "puffed up with vanity",
      "answer": "grandiloquent"
    },
    {
      "question": "an Eskimo hut",
      "answer": "igloo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strong odor or taste property",
      "answer": "pungency"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of soiling something  ",
      "answer": "soiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "not consciously observing",
      "answer": "unobservant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a punch made of sweetened ale or wine heated with spices and roasted apples",
      "answer": "wassail"
    },
    {
      "question": "make whiter or lighter",
      "answer": "bleach"
    },
    {
      "question": "liquid preparation having a soothing or antiseptic or medicinal action when applied to the skin",
      "answer": "lotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of geology that studies minerals: their structure and properties and the ways of distinguishing them  ",
      "answer": "mineralogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an airplane with a single wing  ",
      "answer": "monoplane"
    },
    {
      "question": "the side or slope of a mountain",
      "answer": "mountainside"
    },
    {
      "question": "a breeding ground for gregarious birds (such as rooks)  ",
      "answer": "rookery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a daughter of your spouse by a former marriage  ",
      "answer": "stepdaughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "ingenuousness by virtue of being free from artful deceit  ",
      "answer": "artlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a clean and distinct outline as if precisely cut along the edges",
      "answer": "chiseled"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is part mortal and part god  ",
      "answer": "daemon"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a manner impossible to cure",
      "answer": "incurably"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by formation of a membrane (or something resembling a membrane)",
      "answer": "membranous"
    },
    {
      "question": "the political orientation of those who favor revolutionary change in government and society  ",
      "answer": "radicalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "shod with slippers  ",
      "answer": "slippered"
    },
    {
      "question": "cohabitation without being legally married  ",
      "answer": "concubinage"
    },
    {
      "question": "grasping and shaking a person's hand (as to acknowledge an introduction or to agree on a contract)  ",
      "answer": "handshake"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occupation of a plumber (installing and repairing pipes and fixtures for water or gas or sewage in a building)  ",
      "answer": "plumbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the layer of soil between the topsoil and bedrock  ",
      "answer": "subsoil"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of taking the place of another especially using underhanded tactics  ",
      "answer": "supplanting"
    },
    {
      "question": "devoid of matter",
      "answer": "vacuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of annoyance at being hindered or criticized",
      "answer": "frustration"
    },
    {
      "question": "inhale recreational drugs",
      "answer": "huff"
    },
    {
      "question": "inflicting punishment",
      "answer": "punitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "the reduction of expenditures in order to become financially stable  ",
      "answer": "retrenchment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a streamlined enclosure for an aircraft engine  ",
      "answer": "nacelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or denoting numbers",
      "answer": "numeral"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small sphere  ",
      "answer": "pellet"
    },
    {
      "question": "make too low an estimate of",
      "answer": "underestimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a false accusation of an offense or a malicious misrepresentation of someone's words or actions  ",
      "answer": "defamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "with complete identity",
      "answer": "identically"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an impersonal manner",
      "answer": "impersonally"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being able to cope with a difficult situation",
      "answer": "resourcefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being rustic or gauche  ",
      "answer": "rusticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sensitive manner",
      "answer": "sensitively"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unalterable and unchangeable manner",
      "answer": "unalterably"
    },
    {
      "question": "meriting respect or esteem",
      "answer": "upstanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system of weights based on the 16-ounce pound (or 7,000 grains)  ",
      "answer": "avoirdupois"
    },
    {
      "question": "a craftsman skilled in building with bricks  ",
      "answer": "bricklayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "tamper, with the purpose of deception",
      "answer": "fudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a labyrinth in form or complexity",
      "answer": "labyrinthine"
    },
    {
      "question": "knowledgeable and educated in one or several fields",
      "answer": "literate"
    },
    {
      "question": "destroy or injure severely",
      "answer": "mutilate"
    },
    {
      "question": "express one's opinion openly and without fear or hesitation",
      "answer": "opine"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various willows having pliable twigs used in basketry and furniture  ",
      "answer": "osier"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the chest or thorax",
      "answer": "pectoral"
    },
    {
      "question": "an apparatus for removing impurities  ",
      "answer": "purifier"
    },
    {
      "question": "a portable box-shaped free-reed instrument",
      "answer": "accordion"
    },
    {
      "question": "the dead skin at the base of a fingernail or toenail  ",
      "answer": "cuticle"
    },
    {
      "question": "one having both male and female sexual characteristics and organs",
      "answer": "hermaphrodite"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme excess",
      "answer": "overplus"
    },
    {
      "question": "an offensive term for Roman Catholics",
      "answer": "papist"
    },
    {
      "question": "plant or grow in a fixed cyclic order of succession",
      "answer": "rotate"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a superlative degree  ",
      "answer": "superlatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "not associated in an exclusive sexual relationship  ",
      "answer": "unattached"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man-made receptacle that houses a swarm of bees  ",
      "answer": "beehive"
    },
    {
      "question": "an item of factual information derived from measurement or research  ",
      "answer": "datum"
    },
    {
      "question": "refrain from doing",
      "answer": "forbear"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who provides the means for subsistence  ",
      "answer": "provider"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpredictably excitable (especially of horses)  ",
      "answer": "skittish"
    },
    {
      "question": "rule or exercise power over (somebody) in a cruel and autocratic manner",
      "answer": "tyrannize"
    },
    {
      "question": "not firmly fastened or secured",
      "answer": "unbarred"
    },
    {
      "question": "an island consisting of a circular coral reef surrounding a lagoon  ",
      "answer": "atoll"
    },
    {
      "question": "formed by the coalescence of particles  ",
      "answer": "concrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of head  ",
      "answer": "headship"
    },
    {
      "question": "not practical",
      "answer": "impractical"
    },
    {
      "question": "all the time",
      "answer": "interminably"
    },
    {
      "question": "enthusiastic and assured vigor and liveliness",
      "answer": "elan"
    },
    {
      "question": "the outer layer of the skin covering the exterior body surface of vertebrates  ",
      "answer": "epidermis"
    },
    {
      "question": "any connection or unifying bond  ",
      "answer": "ligament"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing or able to cause nausea",
      "answer": "nauseating"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman protege  ",
      "answer": "protegee"
    },
    {
      "question": "move a liquid from one container into another by means of a siphon or a siphoning action",
      "answer": "siphon"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no limits in range or scope",
      "answer": "unlimited"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to a condition",
      "answer": "conditionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of physics that deals with the emission and effects of electrons and with the use of electronic devices  ",
      "answer": "electronics"
    },
    {
      "question": "a light-sensitive coating on paper or film",
      "answer": "emulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "taking heed",
      "answer": "heedful"
    },
    {
      "question": "the dominance or leadership of one social group or nation over others",
      "answer": "hegemony"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strip of level paved surface where planes can take off and land  ",
      "answer": "runway"
    },
    {
      "question": "not arousing emotions  ",
      "answer": "unmoving"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of copying or making a duplicate (or duplicates) of something",
      "answer": "duplication"
    },
    {
      "question": "take out of a literary work in order to cite or copy  ",
      "answer": "excerpt"
    },
    {
      "question": "of dark brownish to purplish red  ",
      "answer": "maroon"
    },
    {
      "question": "not bound by shackles and chains  ",
      "answer": "unchained"
    },
    {
      "question": "the appearance of truth",
      "answer": "verisimilitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "form into a wreath  ",
      "answer": "wreathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "lettuce with long dark-green leaves in a loosely packed elongated head  ",
      "answer": "cos"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an equitable manner",
      "answer": "equitably"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the science of genetics",
      "answer": "genetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "not working or taking effect",
      "answer": "inoperative"
    },
    {
      "question": "having thin strips of lead between the lines of type  ",
      "answer": "leaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flat cake of thin batter fried on both sides on a griddle  ",
      "answer": "pancake"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stanza of four lines  ",
      "answer": "quatrain"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activities involved in selling commodities directly to consumers  ",
      "answer": "retailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Spanish mackerel of western North America  ",
      "answer": "sierra"
    },
    {
      "question": "not converted  ",
      "answer": "unconverted"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by columns",
      "answer": "columnar"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being shaped or bent or drawn out",
      "answer": "ductile"
    },
    {
      "question": "made local or oriented locally",
      "answer": "localized"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust again after an initial failure  ",
      "answer": "readjust"
    },
    {
      "question": "not smiling  ",
      "answer": "unsmiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes candies and other sweets  ",
      "answer": "confectioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a utensil for cooking  ",
      "answer": "cooker"
    },
    {
      "question": "the temporal property of being cut short  ",
      "answer": "curtailment"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or determined by geometry  ",
      "answer": "geometric"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or affected by prejudice or envy or distaste",
      "answer": "jaundiced"
    },
    {
      "question": "be in a huff and display one's displeasure",
      "answer": "sulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "having parts that slide one within another",
      "answer": "telescopic"
    },
    {
      "question": "without extravagance",
      "answer": "temperately"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or constituting vertebrae  ",
      "answer": "vertebral"
    },
    {
      "question": "a document that serves as evidence of some expenditure  ",
      "answer": "voucher"
    },
    {
      "question": "blue North American songbird  ",
      "answer": "bluebird"
    },
    {
      "question": "wilfully obstinate",
      "answer": "contumacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "ancient Italian deity in human shape, with horns, pointed ears and a goat's tail",
      "answer": "faun"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking distinguishing characteristics or features",
      "answer": "featureless"
    },
    {
      "question": "having legs of a specified kind or number",
      "answer": "legged"
    },
    {
      "question": "infested with lice",
      "answer": "lousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "injure or wound seriously and leave permanent disfiguration or mutilation",
      "answer": "maim"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from physical desire",
      "answer": "platonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the skills involved in the work of a priest  ",
      "answer": "priestcraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "rub with pumice, in order to clean or to smoothen  ",
      "answer": "pumice"
    },
    {
      "question": "masonry done with stone  ",
      "answer": "stonework"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large bonnet that shades the face",
      "answer": "sunbonnet"
    },
    {
      "question": "mammary gland of bovids (cows and sheep and goats)  ",
      "answer": "udder"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk leisurely  ",
      "answer": "amble"
    },
    {
      "question": " aggressively self-assured",
      "answer": "assertive"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a living organism in organization or development",
      "answer": "integrated"
    },
    {
      "question": "a building (or room) where dead bodies are kept before burial or cremation  ",
      "answer": "morgue"
    },
    {
      "question": "made from juice of sweet sorghum  ",
      "answer": "sorghum"
    },
    {
      "question": "willing to carry out the orders or wishes of another without protest",
      "answer": "acquiescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "chew the cuds",
      "answer": "ruminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust (sails on a ship) so that the wind is optimally used  ",
      "answer": "trim"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person addicted to luxury and pleasures of the senses  ",
      "answer": "voluptuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "assigning to a cause or source",
      "answer": "attribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "move or cause to move energetically or busily",
      "answer": "bustle"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who lives in a cottage  ",
      "answer": "cottager"
    },
    {
      "question": "native to or confined to a certain region",
      "answer": "endemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or promoting the preaching and dissemination of the Christian gospel",
      "answer": "evangelistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an innocent quality or thing or act",
      "answer": "innocency"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fortress established in the southwestern United States by the Spanish in order to protect their missions and other holdings",
      "answer": "presidio"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used especially of merchandise) very fine in quality",
      "answer": "superfine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wainscoted wall (or wainscoted walls collectively)  ",
      "answer": "wainscoting"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short poem descriptive of rural or pastoral life  ",
      "answer": "eclogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "a decorative coating of contrasting material that is applied to a surface as an inlay or overlay  ",
      "answer": "incrustation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the outside boundary or surface of something  ",
      "answer": "periphery"
    },
    {
      "question": "sordid dirtiness  ",
      "answer": "sordidness"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform an autopsy on a dead body",
      "answer": "autopsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that strongly attracts attention and admiration",
      "answer": "cynosure"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the partial taking away of the effectiveness of a law",
      "answer": "derogation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vowel sound that starts near the articulatory position for one vowel and moves toward the position for another  ",
      "answer": "diphthong"
    },
    {
      "question": "without a fault",
      "answer": "faultlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of grouping things or people in pairs  ",
      "answer": "pairing"
    },
    {
      "question": "drawn or written with a pencil",
      "answer": "penciled"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from emotional appeal",
      "answer": "unimpassioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "a game in which jackstones are thrown and picked up in various groups between bounces of a small rubber ball  ",
      "answer": "jacks"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking or showing a lack of what is fitting and considerate in dealing with others",
      "answer": "tactless"
    },
    {
      "question": "tropical starchy tuberous root  ",
      "answer": "taro"
    },
    {
      "question": "a blunt needle for threading ribbon through loops  ",
      "answer": "bodkin"
    },
    {
      "question": "the style of expressing yourself",
      "answer": "formulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mania restricted to one thing or idea  ",
      "answer": "monomania"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely and sharply",
      "answer": "piercingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unselfish manner",
      "answer": "unselfishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "warding off",
      "answer": "cautionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not being usable  ",
      "answer": "impracticability"
    },
    {
      "question": "impart vigor, strength, or vitality to",
      "answer": "invigorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thorough search for something (often causing disorder or confusion)",
      "answer": "ransacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "getting rid of a stage of a multistage rocket  ",
      "answer": "staging"
    },
    {
      "question": "a natural disposition to be hostile  ",
      "answer": "aggressiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "player acts out a phrase for others to guess  ",
      "answer": "charades"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who sets written material into type  ",
      "answer": "compositor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small fipple flute with four finger holes and two thumb holes  ",
      "answer": "flageolet"
    },
    {
      "question": "not adroit",
      "answer": "maladroit"
    },
    {
      "question": "loose hemp or jute fiber obtained by unravelling old ropes",
      "answer": "oakum"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the pituitary gland",
      "answer": "pituitary"
    },
    {
      "question": "inclined to or marked by drowsiness",
      "answer": "slumberous"
    },
    {
      "question": "impose or inflict forcefully",
      "answer": "clamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "disagreeing, especially with a majority  ",
      "answer": "dissentient"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly the chief magistrate in the republics of Venice and Genoa  ",
      "answer": "doge"
    },
    {
      "question": "something of sentimental value  ",
      "answer": "keepsake"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly the basic unit of money in Italy",
      "answer": "lira"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of becoming mellow  ",
      "answer": "mellowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "traveling especially on foot",
      "answer": "peripatetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) the appearance of text and graphics on a video display  ",
      "answer": "video"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepare or cook by mixing ingredients",
      "answer": "concoct"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the consecration from a person or an object  ",
      "answer": "desecrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "suck milk from the mother's breasts",
      "answer": "suckle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not being important or worthy of note  ",
      "answer": "unimportance"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a disproportionate degree",
      "answer": "disproportionately"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a questioning format  ",
      "answer": "interrogatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "be present at an event and see it with one's own eyes  ",
      "answer": "eyewitness"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a focus",
      "answer": "focal"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or affecting or functioning as a gland",
      "answer": "glandular"
    },
    {
      "question": "form ideals",
      "answer": "idealize"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an impudent or impertinent manner",
      "answer": "impertinently"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone subject to melancholia  ",
      "answer": "melancholic"
    },
    {
      "question": "having partial financial support from public funds",
      "answer": "subsidized"
    },
    {
      "question": "estimate the value of (property) for taxation",
      "answer": "assess"
    },
    {
      "question": "a place or condition in which no development or progress is occurring",
      "answer": "backwater"
    },
    {
      "question": "of great mass",
      "answer": "elephantine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a young woman in the 1920s who flaunted her unconventional conduct and dress  ",
      "answer": "flapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "an infant considered in relation to its nurse  ",
      "answer": "nursling"
    },
    {
      "question": "eating until excessively full  ",
      "answer": "repletion"
    },
    {
      "question": "shave the head of a newly inducted monk  ",
      "answer": "tonsure"
    },
    {
      "question": "any woodland plant of the genus Anemone grown for its beautiful flowers and whorls of dissected leaves  ",
      "answer": "anemone"
    },
    {
      "question": "gruesomely indicative of death or the dead",
      "answer": "charnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "a paving stone forming part of a curb  ",
      "answer": "curbstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of a freak",
      "answer": "freakish"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a suggestive manner",
      "answer": "suggestively"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman ancestor  ",
      "answer": "ancestress"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person with great powers and abilities  ",
      "answer": "demigod"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who travels by air  ",
      "answer": "flier"
    },
    {
      "question": "equipment and supplies of a military force  ",
      "answer": "materiel"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing numbness or insensitivity",
      "answer": "numbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "reason philosophically  ",
      "answer": "philosophize"
    },
    {
      "question": "an expert in strategy (especially in warfare)  ",
      "answer": "strategist"
    },
    {
      "question": "not knowable",
      "answer": "unknowable"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unplanned expedient  ",
      "answer": "improvisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a structure shaped like a funnel in the outlet of the kidney into which urine is discharged before passing into the ureter  ",
      "answer": "pelvis"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a rim or a rim of a specified kind",
      "answer": "rimmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "sprinkled with seed",
      "answer": "seeded"
    },
    {
      "question": "pertaining to or containing or consisting of semen",
      "answer": "seminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a salt or ester of acetic acid  ",
      "answer": "acetate"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling human beings  ",
      "answer": "anthropoid"
    },
    {
      "question": "the terminal section of the alimentary canal",
      "answer": "rectum"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tunic worn over a knight's armor  ",
      "answer": "surcoat"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pointed tool for marking surfaces or for punching small holes  ",
      "answer": "awl"
    },
    {
      "question": "the consistency of a compact solid  ",
      "answer": "compactness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in your mind",
      "answer": "mentally"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with a base, support, lining, or backing",
      "answer": "underlay"
    },
    {
      "question": "the consequences of an event (especially a catastrophic event)",
      "answer": "aftermath"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sound elements of television  ",
      "answer": "audio"
    },
    {
      "question": "social or verbal interchange (usually followed by `with')  ",
      "answer": "dealings"
    },
    {
      "question": "the official residence of a dean  ",
      "answer": "deanery"
    },
    {
      "question": "an appearance that has been spoiled or is misshapen",
      "answer": "disfigurement"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cocktail made of gin or vodka and lime juice  ",
      "answer": "gimlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "make pregnant",
      "answer": "impregnate"
    },
    {
      "question": "Eurasian plant widely cultivated for its edible pungent root usually eaten raw  ",
      "answer": "radish"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose business is to supply a particular service or commodity  ",
      "answer": "supplier"
    },
    {
      "question": "becoming gradually narrower",
      "answer": "tapered"
    },
    {
      "question": "not brought under control",
      "answer": "unsubdued"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long stiff hair growing from the snout or brow of most mammals as e.g. a cat  ",
      "answer": "whisker"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing food and services  ",
      "answer": "catering"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an insane manner",
      "answer": "insanely"
    },
    {
      "question": "delicate and pale in color",
      "answer": "pastel"
    },
    {
      "question": "a filter to retain larger pieces while smaller pieces and liquids pass through  ",
      "answer": "strainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a swing used by circus acrobats  ",
      "answer": "trapeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "loosen the ties of",
      "answer": "unloose"
    },
    {
      "question": "not characteristic of or befitting a profession or one engaged in a profession",
      "answer": "unprofessional"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or expressing accusation",
      "answer": "accusative"
    },
    {
      "question": "close with a cork or stopper  ",
      "answer": "bung"
    },
    {
      "question": "a red dyestuff consisting of dried bodies of female cochineal insects  ",
      "answer": "cochineal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a photograph made by an early photographic process",
      "answer": "daguerreotype"
    },
    {
      "question": "free somebody (from an erroneous belief)  ",
      "answer": "disabuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "freeing from false belief or illusions  ",
      "answer": "disenchantment"
    },
    {
      "question": "give or delegate power or authority to",
      "answer": "empower"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inclination to favor some person or group  ",
      "answer": "favoritism"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several North American species of small pike  ",
      "answer": "pickerel"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an affected manner  ",
      "answer": "affectedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a child secretly exchanged for another in infancy  ",
      "answer": "changeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "make clear by removing impurities or solids, as by heating",
      "answer": "clarify"
    },
    {
      "question": "yielding a fair profit  ",
      "answer": "gainful"
    },
    {
      "question": "small tubular solitary freshwater hydrozoan polyp  ",
      "answer": "hydra"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an officious manner",
      "answer": "officiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "take off or away",
      "answer": "subtract"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a surpassing degree",
      "answer": "surpassingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing hostility or loss of friendliness",
      "answer": "alienating"
    },
    {
      "question": "the excretory opening at the end of the alimentary canal  ",
      "answer": "anus"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several evergreen shrubs of the genus Arbutus of temperate Europe and America  ",
      "answer": "arbutus"
    },
    {
      "question": "(basketball) a player releases the basketball at the high point of a jump  ",
      "answer": "jumper"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is discontented or disgusted  ",
      "answer": "malcontent"
    },
    {
      "question": "sudden prostration due to exposure to the sun or excessive heat  ",
      "answer": "sunstroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "not disposed of by purchase",
      "answer": "unsold"
    },
    {
      "question": "push or shove upward, as if from below or behind",
      "answer": "boost"
    },
    {
      "question": "the craft of a carpenter: making things out of wood  ",
      "answer": "carpentry"
    },
    {
      "question": "supply food ready to eat",
      "answer": "cater"
    },
    {
      "question": "weakening (reducing the concentration) by the addition of water or a thinner  ",
      "answer": "dilution"
    },
    {
      "question": "a predisposition to like something",
      "answer": "fondness"
    },
    {
      "question": "one-hundredth of a right angle  ",
      "answer": "grad"
    },
    {
      "question": "an organic compound containing only carbon and hydrogen  ",
      "answer": "hydrocarbon"
    },
    {
      "question": "the baggage and equipment carried by an army  ",
      "answer": "impedimenta"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a mistaken manner",
      "answer": "mistakenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the art of making perfumes  ",
      "answer": "perfumery"
    },
    {
      "question": "the portion of the loin (especially of beef) just in front of the rump  ",
      "answer": "sirloin"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a will or testament or bequeathed by a will or testament  ",
      "answer": "testamentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring to light",
      "answer": "unearth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a party who files a notice with a law court  ",
      "answer": "filer"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a fretful manner",
      "answer": "fretfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "interpret falsely  ",
      "answer": "misinterpret"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hinged airfoil on the upper surface of an aircraft wing that is raised to reduce lift and increase drag  ",
      "answer": "spoiler"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a tail of a specified kind",
      "answer": "tailed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the attribute of having been domesticated  ",
      "answer": "tameness"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who bounds or leaps (as in competition)  ",
      "answer": "bounder"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who disputes",
      "answer": "disputant"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of mechanics concerned with the forces that cause motions of bodies  ",
      "answer": "dynamics"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of conforming to law  ",
      "answer": "lawfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "make dark, dim, or gloomy  ",
      "answer": "murk"
    },
    {
      "question": "changing an arrangement  ",
      "answer": "rearrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "large and brightly colored handkerchief",
      "answer": "bandanna"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nihilistic art movement (especially in painting) that flourished in Europe early in the 20th century",
      "answer": "dada"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of eighty in counting order  ",
      "answer": "eightieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "an acute streptococcal infection characterized by deep-red inflammation of the skin and mucous membranes  ",
      "answer": "erysipelas"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large piece of something without definite shape",
      "answer": "hunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "put under water",
      "answer": "submerge"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to decrease or cause a decrease in value",
      "answer": "depreciating"
    },
    {
      "question": "candy made of a thick creamy sugar paste  ",
      "answer": "fondant"
    },
    {
      "question": "build with groins",
      "answer": "groin"
    },
    {
      "question": "any tree or shrub of the genus Inga having pinnate leaves and showy usually white flowers",
      "answer": "inga"
    },
    {
      "question": "wildly disordered",
      "answer": "maniacal"
    },
    {
      "question": "large semi-evergreen tree of the East Indies",
      "answer": "neem"
    },
    {
      "question": "proportionate  ",
      "answer": "proportionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "in terms of psychology",
      "answer": "psychologically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a purging medicine",
      "answer": "purgative"
    }
  ]
}